msupayment.in 2018-11-05

# 

This Privacy Policy and Terms of Use is effective from 12th March 2017
Manonmaniam Sundaranar University, Tirunelveli ("University") is committed to protecting
your privacy and accelerating online facilitation of quicker and reliable communication to
the applicants who are to submit examination application and pay fees online for April-May
2017 examinations by using third party innovative online solutions.
This Privacy Policy and Terms of Use (“Policy & Terms”) applies to those persons (“Students”)
 who submit online examination application and pay exam fee for the examinations examinations
to be conducted by the University during April and May 2017 and visiting Manonmaniam
Sundaranar University website and www.msupayment.in to have access of the web interface
(“Website”) that contain relevant application format fields to be filled in online and submit the
same as well as to make online payment of the required fee and convenience charge through
authenticated login (“Service”). The service offered by the website is meant only for
the relevant applicants both current and private students entering his/her details to apply for
appearing in the April and May 2017 examinations as per the time table published by the
University. The applicant students of current batches are required to provide the registration
number, email ID and mobile number as part of online submission of application. As soon as the
above details are submitted, he / she will be allowed with a valid OTP ( one time
password) the access to the interface for transaction. In the case of current students the interface
would display the pre existing details regarding the subjects to appear for the examinations so as
to confirm and pay the fees. The private students are also allowed access in the same manner and
he/she has to provide various details about the subject code etc to appear for the examinations
and pay the fee. Any person other than an applicant student as stated above is specifically
prohibited to use or attempt to use the service.
For providing you an authenticated access, we collect your mobile number that belongs to you
or currently being used by you or authorized to be used by you as mandatory requirement. On
submitting the mobile number, you will be receiving One Time Password (OTP) in the mobile
entered by you for verification and authentication. On applying the OTP received, you will be
provided an authenticated access for using the service. The information submitted by you is
used for the Service and will be used only for the purpose meant here.
At the end of online application with details for submission, you will be asked to declare the
statement as shown in the screen as well as agree to the Policy & Terms to further proceed to use
the service and confirm the submission. If the displayed details in the screen before the
declaration do not match to your details or what you have provided, you may provide additional
information as allowed by the interface or do the edit, if allowed by the interface and change the
details OR If you do not agree to the declaration and / or the Policy & Terms (you are advised to
click open and read the same), then you shall revert back by clicking the “Cancel” button
                           AQSS/120317/VER/1.1 ISSUE DATE 12/03/2017

available in that web page. NO PERSON SHOULD USE OR ATTEMPT TO USE THE
SERVICE KNOWINGLY THAT THE DETAILS ENTERED AND / OR THE DETAILS
DISPLAYED ON THE SAID SCREEN                     DONOT BELONG TO HIM/HER, THEN SUCH
PERSON IS PROHIBITED TO CONFIRM THE DETAILS TO PROCEED FURTHER AND
DOING SO WOULD AMOUNT TO VIOLATION OF THE TERMS OF USE AND LIABLE
FOR APPROPRIATE ACTION BOTH LEGAL AND CIVIL AS THE CASE MAY BE. Once
the submitted details are of yours and complete as well as you agree to the declaration and Policy
& Terms, then you may click the “Confirm” button after ticking the check box provided therein.
 If any applicant ticks the check box and clicks “Confirm” button, it is concluded that he/she
had made the declaration and agreed to the Policy & Terms. In case you have anything to resolve
in this regard, please contact by email furnished in the website.
In the case of private students, your intended use of the service for the first time itself, the mobile
number entered by you will be registered and linked to your details for future authentication
also. Hence you are advised to enter only Indian mobile number that is being used by you or
authorized to be used by you. Anyone trying or attempting to violate this mandatory requirement
may be treated as violating the Policy & Terms and liable for appropriate legal and civil action as
the case may be.
Once you confirm and proceed to make the payment, you will be directed to a third party served
secured socket layer web page to do the payment transaction of the required fee and convenience
charge. By choosing any one of the mode of payment options namely by credit card or debit card
or through net banking as the case may be, you can complete your payment. Once payment is
successful, you will be directed to page where you can download your application in PDF format
for your record. Depending upon the choice of the mode of payment the convenience charge
may vary. While transacting the payment, you are required to provide only the credit / debit card
or net banking details that are genuine. Any applicant trying or attempting to misuse this page
will be treated as violating the terms of usage and liable for both civil & criminal legal action.
 By choosing to proceed with payment and visiting the relevant web page of the payment
gateway provider, you are also bound by their terms of usage and privacy policy.
We have the discretion to capture other information such as end user device models, IP, usage
pattern etc for analytical purpose and improving the service. The content of your information
shall be retained and used for future communication; conduct of examination and shall be
available for limited period as determined by the University
You may note that third party software is used for analytics of usage of this site. All matrix
information collected from your usage of the Service shall be used for improving the service and
evaluating as to how the users use the service to compile statistical information. The matrix
information and statistical information shall never be divulged to you for any reasons
whatsoever. We will use this information in order to maintain, enhance, or add to the
functionality of the Service and to personalize the experience for you.
                            AQSS/120317/VER/1.1 ISSUE DATE 12/03/2017

When you use the website or service we may store some information on your computer. This
information will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of
information stored on your hard drive. These cookies are essential for the basic functionalities
offered by the Service. Various categories of cookies (including third party cookies) are used in
the website and Service. We do not use cookies to spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy.
They cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. We use cookies to help you navigate
the website and service as easily as possible, and to remember information about your current
session. These are the Session Cookies and they are removed from your system when you close
the web browser or turn off the computer. You may also note that an advice has been provided
in the website as to which of the browsers are supported by the website for optimal
performance and you shall access using these browsers only. Also you should follow the
instruction given in the index page of the website to successfully complete the online
submission. You must enable cookies, if required, on your web browser to use the Service. You
can set your browser to either reject all cookies, to allow only “trusted” websites to set them, or
to accept only those cookies from those websites you are currently on.
The Website and Service have the required standard security measures in place to protect against
the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing
as “perfect security” on the Internet, we take all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your
personal information. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot
guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the website or via the Service and any
transmission is at your own risk. Once we receive your personal information, we will use strict
procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. Additionally, you retain
all rights of ownership to your personal data we collect. Except as set forth herein, we will not
sell or share your personal data with any third parties or use your personal data to compete with
you. Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. We retain your data as long as needed to
provide the Service. We reserve the right to disclose your personal data as required by applicable
law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with
a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process served on us.
Amendments to the Policy & Terms will be posted to this URL and will be effective when
posted.
If you have questions or clarification regarding the service please send email to
msuexamapplicationhelp@gmail.com
The Privacy Policy and Terms of Use are governed by Indian laws and subject to Jurisdiction of
appropriate courts in India.
                             AQSS/120317/VER/1.1 ISSUE DATE 12/03/2017
